美国好声音决赛现场现在开始
第七季 第二十七集
今晚 "美国好声音"的冠军将会诞生
各位好 我是Carson Daly 欢迎收看决赛现场
接着介绍我们的导师们 Adam Levine先生
Gwen Stefani
Pharrell Williams
还有Blake Shelton
接着请出决赛选手 来自Blake战队的Craig Wayne Boyd
还有来自Adam战队的Chris Jamison
Damien
还有Matt McAndrew.
今晚 其中一位决赛选手的愿望将会实现
即将迎来一个难以置信的夜晚 表演者有格莱美奖和奥斯卡奖获得者
包括Jennifer Hudson Hozier Fall out boy Mark Ronson Bruno Mars
Lynyrd Skynyrd Meghan Trainer Jessie J还有Ed sheeran都将登台演出
还有前20强选手重新齐聚一堂
节目开始之前 还有导师们带来的特别演出
一起回顾一下昨晚进行的精彩演出吧
昨晚 好声音四强选手在上台进行了最后一次竞赛表演
带来榜首原唱歌曲的首秀
Blake战队与Adam战队一决雌雄的时刻到了
能得知全美观众的选择让我很激动 选手们都很棒 都应该获胜
欢迎来到你的未来
这首歌就是为你量身打造
我完全沉迷你的表演之中了 谢谢你 真的让我很有灵感
这是我一生中听过最棒的歌曲之一
歌词我都知道 我爱你 哥们
一个巨星就要在这里诞生了 等不及想看你以后的作品了 太棒了
我是世上最快乐的导师 不论成败 全世界都在我手中了
他们与导师进行了让人印象深刻的合唱
与Craig同台演出是我职业生涯中最激动的演出之一 他真的很棒
-现在我们要一起去巡演了  -是的
我的队员们 都很特别
都充满精力 独一无二
我为他们的进步而骄傲 他们真正蜕变成为了明星
你上台表演了 成为一个表演家 那就是你的歌曲
四位决赛选手在舞台上全力以赴
为大家的投票而奋斗
今晚真的很吸引 真的很棒 所有人都表现的很棒
作为一个音乐制作人 我认为他们都很棒
我年轻的绝地武士("星球大战"中角色) 欢迎你 祝贺
你唱这首歌的方式把我带到了教堂
真的很有感情
乡村音乐的关键在于真实
整个世界都为之停顿 享受你如此完美纯净的声音
-真的太棒了 比我们排练时更棒  -酷
本季最重要的夜晚终于来临了
大家的投票已经清点 好声音的冠军就要诞生
第七季的决赛现在开始
这是享受音乐与进行投票的夜晚
决赛选手们在iTunes上创下纪录
首秀的每首歌都登上了单曲榜前10 这太棒了
事实上 昨晚每一首歌曲都登上了榜单前50
这简直出乎意料 真的让我们无比骄傲
继续今晚的音乐盛宴吧
开场的将会是大家的本季最爱环节
欢迎前20强为大家带来"Pompeii"
-歌曲:Pompeii  原唱:Bastille
#eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o#
#I was left to my own devices#
#many days fell away with nothing to show#
#and the walls kept tumbling down in the city that we love#
#great clouds roll over the hills bringing darkness from above#
#but if you close your eyes does it almost feel like nothing changed at all#
#And if you close your eyes does it almost feel like you'Ve been here before#
#How am I gonna be an optimist about this#
#how am I gonna be an optimist about this#
#eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o#
#oh where do we begin the rubble or our sins#
#oh,oh where do we begin the rubble or our sins#
#And the walls kept tumbling down oh where do we begin#
#In the city that we love the rubble or our sins#
#great clouds roll over the hills oh where do we begin the rubble or our sins#
#but if you close your eyes#
#does it almost feel like nothing changed at all#
#and if you close your eyes#
#does it almost feel like you'Ve been here before#
#how am I gonna be an optimist about this#
#If you close your eyes does it almost feel like nothing changed at all#
#Eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o#
#eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o eh-eh-o eh-o#
很高兴看到各位归来 掌声送给前20强
休息之后 Craig Wayne Boyd将与本季同伴带来精彩表演
稍后欢迎Hozier Fall out boy Mark Ronson Bruno Mars Lynyrd Skynyrd
Meghan Trainer Jennifer Hudson Jessie J还有Ed sheeran的表演
是的 冠军将在今夜诞生 很快回来 你正在收看的是NBC
欢迎继续收看美国好声音决赛之夜
稍后 我们即将公布最终冠军
先与导师们聊一下吧 先从你开始 Adam Levine
恭喜 这一季真是太棒了
今晚有你队的三位选手
说一下这一季如此成功的秘诀吧
没有秘诀 重点就是大家都合作的很好
选手们都愿意听我的意见并让我教导他们
我真的很为他们骄傲 昨晚我过得很愉快
恭喜你 这一季取得的成绩真的很棒
Gwen Stefani 你能加入好声音大家庭真的很让人激动
你对此感觉怎么样
我现在还在慢慢消化一切 真不敢相信自己能在这里
是在是太快了 真的很棒
-感谢大家邀请我来  -谢谢
Shelton 一会再说你
Pharrell 你身为音乐制作人
你今晚要给选手们什么样的建议
我对每个人都这样说 每个人都会在某一时刻回家
重点是想到明天要进行的下一步计划
对我来说 这个节目就是一个平台 让大家有机会拥有世界
很好的建议 来自最棒的人 谢谢你 Pharrell
Blake Shelton 你今晚有多自信
Craig能够战胜几率 做些特别的表演
我不知道今晚会发生什么事
我...不清楚自己有多自信
我感觉Craig为了获胜已经全力以赴了
我不知道会发生什么
但我现在紧张的要死 你要是想问这个的话
谢谢你 Blake 谢谢导师们
现在将请出大家最喜欢的表演家
Craig决定在最后一次表演中与最喜欢的选手们同台
我这一次想表演The Georgia Satellites的"Keep Your Hands to Yourself"
我想与Danica Sugar和Taylor同台
他们身上具备演绎这首歌的特点
我觉得我们的合作会很棒
Dannika是我在参加节目过程中的依靠
她是声线很特别 她是音域也无人能及
Sugar的嗓音非常特别 任何人都不能匹敌
我觉得她演唱Aregentha Franklin的"Say a Little Prayer for You"时
真的非常棒 也让我相信了她的实力
Taylor和我度过了一些疯狂而美好的日子
她总是能逗我笑
她也是Blake队的 她的特殊音质
会很适合这首歌
能把她们都带回来 我很激动
和她们一起同台演唱 我们一定会轰动全场
好了 下一首歌是"Keep Your Hands to Yourself"
演唱者为Craig Danica Sugar以及Taylor Brashears
歌曲:Keep Your Hands to Yourself  原唱:The Georgia Satellites
大家嗨起来
#I got a little change in my pocket#
#going jing-a-lang-a-ling#
#Want to call you on the telephone,baby#
#give you a ring#
#but each time we talk#
#I get the same old thing#
#she said,"no huggy,no kissy#
#until I get a wedding ring"#
#My honey,my baby don't put my love upon no shelf#
#she said "don't hand me no lines and keep your#
#hands to yourself"#
#cruel baby,baby,baby#
#why you want to treat me this way#
#You know I'm still your lover boy#
#I still feel the same way#
#I told you a story#
#'bout free milk and a cow#
#and said "no huggy#
#no kissy until I get a wedding vow"#
#My honey,my baby don't put my love upon no shelf#
#I said"don't hand me no lines#
#and keep your hands to yourself"#
#see I wanted#
#her real bad and I was about to give in#
#And that's when she started talkin' about true love#
#started talkin' about sin#
#he said#
#"honey,I live with you for the rest of my life"#
#I said "no huggy,no kissy#
#until you make me your wife"#
#My honey,my baby don't put my love#
#upon no shelf#
#she said "don't hand me no lines and#
#keep your hands to yourself"#
#cruel baby,baby,baby#
#why you want to treat me this way#
#You know I'm still your lover girl#
#I still feel the same way#
#that's when I#
#told you a story 'bout free milk and a cow#
#And said "no huggy,no kissy#
#until I get a wedding vow"#
#My honey,my baby don't put my love#
#upon no shelf#
#she said"don't hand me no lines and keep your#
#hands to yourself"#
#You see,I wanted#
#her real bad and I was about to give in#
#And that's when she started talkin'#
#about true love#
#started talkin'about sin#
#and I said#
#"honey,I live with you for the rest of my life"#
#I said "no huggy,no kissy#
#until you make me your wife"#
#My honey,my baby don't put my love#
#upon no shelf#
#she said"don't hand me no lines#
#and keep your hands to yourself"#
#my honey,my baby#
#don't put my love upon no shelf#
#She said "don't hand me no lines#
#and keep your hands to yourself"#
Chris Wayne Boyd今晚可够忙的
Danica Sugar Taylor 欢迎你们回来 见到你们很高兴
下节更精彩 Hozier要演唱他的流行歌曲"Take Me To Church"
接下来Fall out boy Mark Ronson Bruno Mars Lynyrd Skynyrd
Meghan Trainer Jessie J以及Sherley将带来表演
即将宣布好声音的冠军 不要走开
美国好声音
欢迎大家来
欢迎来到斯普林休息室 决赛正在进行
上一周呢 我们请大家选出本季最棒的片段
现在呢 我们要宣布几个赢家
请给我击鼓
大家来看一看
最佳片段之一 是路上的"Adam与Blake" 一起来看一看
我们安排一个特别但又有我们风格的表演...不只是在公寓
来个公路旅行演出吧
一起坐车从纽约出发去洛杉矶吧
我们会是新版鸭子王朝(真人秀节目)
最大的电视节目
好了 再选一个
最疯狂的选手反应是...
击鼓 "Elyjah惊呆了"
看一看
不 开玩笑吧
我第一次看到她的时候 以为自己会哭
但是努力控制住了自己 只是尖叫了
-我最喜欢的女歌手 天啊  -谢谢
真不错啊 登录NBC官网 点击关注
感谢我们的朋友斯普林的帮助
当然 还要感谢所有好声音的粉丝
感谢你们一直以来的支持
下面的登台的一位歌手
他的歌曲刚被提名格莱美"年度最佳单曲"
歌曲是"Take Me To Church"
掌声欢迎Hozier
歌曲:Take Me To Church 原唱:Hozier
#my lover's got humor#
#she's the giggle at a funeral#
#knows everybody's disapproval#
#I should've worshiped her sooner#
#if the heavens ever did speak#
#she's the last true mouthpiece#
#every Sunday's getting more bleak#
#a fresh poison each week#
#we were born sick#
#you heard them say it#
#my church offers#
#no absolutes#
#she tells me#
#worship in the bedroom the only heaven#
#I'll be sent to#
#is when I'm alone with you#
#I was born sick#
#but I love it command me to be well#
#A... amen#
#amen amen#
#Take me to church I'll worship like a dog#
#at the shrine of your lies#
#I'll tell you my sins#
#and you can sharpen your knife#
#Offer me that deathless death#
#good God let me give you my life#
#Take me to church I'll worship like a dog#
#at the shrine of your lies#
#I'll tell you my sins#
#and you can sharpen your knife#
#Offer me that deathless death#
#good God let me give you my life#
#No masters or kings when the ritual begins#
#There is no sweeter innocence#
#than our gentle sin#
#in the madness and soil#
#of that sad earthly scene only then I am human#
#only then I am clean#
#oh#
#amen#
#take me to church#
#I'll worship like a dog at the shrine of your lies#
#I'll tell you my sins#
# and you can sharpen your knife#
#offer me that#
#deathless death good God#
#let me give you my life#
#take me to church#
#I'll worship like a dog at the shrine of your lies#
#I'll tell you my sins and you can#
#sharpen your knife#
#offer me that#
#deathless death good God#
#let me give you my life#
大家为Hozier鼓掌
稍后回来 Chris带来了他最好的朋友
之后 我们会在NBC官网上宣布冠军
美国好声音
欢迎回到好声音决赛
今晚 我们将宣布冠军
但是首先呢 Chris Jamison要最后一次登台表演
还带来了自己一直敬佩的天才歌手
这次表演呢 我决定邀请
Luke Wade Ricky Manning Taylor Phelan以及Ryan Sill
演唱"Dedication to My Ex"
这是一首刚更新的全新的歌曲 所以应该很适合我们
Luke Wade 每次表演都很投入
我喜欢他弯下腰去与观众互动的部分
我觉得这一点很棒
我喜欢Ricky非常感性的声音
他唱歌的时候非常动情
我喜欢Taylor的酷
他在台上的肢体语言非常吸引人
我带Ryan Sill回来 是因为他每次高音都很表演的很棒
他很有魅力
我喜欢他表演过后
对着摄像头的严肃表情
非常有趣 我们已经是一家人了
能够同台演出 一起参加决赛
这回一定很特别
由Chris携Luke Ricky Ryan以及Taylor Phelan
一起演唱的"Dedication to my ex"
歌曲:Dedication to my ex  原唱:Lloyd
女士们先生们 请欢迎我的朋友 Chris Jamison先生
#Baby something's on my mind I gotta say it#
#yeah,your lovin'done changed it ain't the same girl#
#and that's a shame a crying shame baby#
#oooh,ain't being funny mm-mm#
#I know another bee's been in that honey#
#Ooh,babe that lovin' done changed#
#it's such a shame girl and that's a shame#
#Who the hell you been giving my loving to,girl#
#Oh,no tell me where that lovin' gone oh,no#
#'cause it don't feel the same no more#
#I miss that lovin' that lovin'#
#that lovin' that lovin'#
#Yeah oh,no#
#how you do me like that,baby#
#Oh,no why is this happening to me oh,no#
#she told me that it was my lovin'#
#I miss that lovin' that lovin'#
#that lovin' that lovin'#
#Oh,no yeah,yeah yeah,yeah#
#she used to be a really special lady my everything#
#I guess she's feeling kinda freaky lately#
#It's such a shame 'cause now that#
#lovin's changed that lovin' changed#
#She used to squeeze me whoo#
#grip me tight enough so she could please me#
#But nah nah now that lovin' changed#
#it's such a shame that lovin' changed#
#No oh,no#
#where did your lovin' go oh,no#
#'cause girl I need to know#
#I miss that lovin' that lovin'#
#that lovin' that lovin'#
#Oh,no it was a one-of-a-kind type of love oh,no#
#I can't believe this chick oh,no#
#How you goin' to be like this#
#I miss that lovin' that lovin'#
#that lovin' that lovin'#
#Oh,no yeah,yeah,yeah,yeah#
#come on oh,no#
#oh,no yeah,yeah,yeah,yeah#
#I miss that lovin' that lovi'#
#that lovin' that lovin'#
#oh,no I can't believe this chick#
#Oh,no she gave away all my all#
#I miss that lovin'that lovin' that lovin'#
#that lovin' oh,no#
#yeah,yeah,yeah,yeah#
把热烈的掌声送给Luke Ricky Ryan Taylor还有Chris
干得好 接下来Mark Ronson Bruno Mars
Matt McAndrew以及Fall out Boy即将登场
美国好声音决赛 千万别走开
美国好声音
欢迎大家回到好声音决赛现场
在本季之前时 Adam曾邀请Fall out Boy的Patrick Stump为顾问
今晚 Matt将于Patrick联手演唱
一首新专辑"American beauty / American psycho"的主打曲"Centuries"
将掌声送给Matt McAndrew和fall out boy.
#Du du du du-du du du #
#some legends are told some turn to dust or to gold #
#But you will remember me remember me for centuries#
#and just one mistake is all it will take#
#we'll go down in history remember me for centuries #
#Remember me for centuries#
#Mummified my teenage dreams no it's nothing wrong with me#
#The kids are all wrong the story's all off heavy metal broke my heart#
#Come on come on and let me in the bruises on your thighs like my fingerprints#
#And this is supposed to match the darkness that you felt#
#I never meant for you to fix yourself#
#Du du du du-du du du#
#Du du du du du-du du du#
#Some legends are told some turn to dust or to gold#
#but you will remember me remember me for centuries#
#And just one mistake is all it will take#
#We'll go down in history remember me for centuries#
#remember me for centuries#
#and I can't stop till the whole world knows my name#
#'Cause I was only born inside my dreams#
#Until you die for me as long as there is a light my shadow's over you#
#'cause I I am the opposite of amnesia#
#And you're a cherry blossom you're about to bloom#
#you look so pretty but you're gone so soon#
#we'Ve been here forever and here's the frozen proof#
#I could scream forever we are the poisoned youth#
#du du du du du-du du du#
#some legends are told some turn to dust or to gold#
#But you will remember me remember me for centuries#
#And just one mistake is all it will take#
#We'll go down in history remember me for centuries#
将掌声送给Matt McAndrew和Fall out boy
很不错 看看Patrick 他会出现在明晚NBC台的"The sing off"
他是一个戴帽子的音乐制作人 有着丰富的经验
本季 你会爱上的是一个谜一般的男人
音乐大师 Pharrell Williams
Pharrell有点像尤达大师(星球大战人物)
这是绝地好声音
不久之前 距离环球播音室不远的地方...
我们的T恤都一样 但我们穿法不同
没有压力 哪里有动力
油漆刷无论如何还有一个油漆刷 油漆刷
Pharrell有点像尤达大师
他总是非常地乐观
这就是我的想法 我的看法
虽然我现在不会尝试 但以后肯定会
他有绝地能力
速度是种错觉 就在你脑海里
他会用智慧看穿别人
你的声音具有你个人的特色
你一个人的时候是什么样 你就是什么样
你必须理解自己
-那会怎么样  -才会存在
没错
顺其自然就好了
而我就是Hans solo(歌手) Blake就是楚巴卡(星球大战人物)
我懂他为什么是Solo(有单独的意思) 因为没人想在他身边
闭嘴吧 楚巴卡
看着我的眼睛
-我选Pharrell  -Pharrell
-Pharrell  -Pharrell
力量与你共存
我们的尤达大师
你都没脸看了
我们都爱你 你是最棒的
好的 本季强势女歌手们将带来"Bang Bang"
掌声欢迎Bryana Danica Jane Mia还有sugar
歌曲:Bang Bang  原唱:Jessie J Ariana Grande & Nicki Minaj
#She got a body like an hourglass but I can give it to you all the time#
#Sugar she got a Booty like a Cadillac but I can send you into overdrive oh#
#You'Ve been waiting for that stop,hold up swing your bat#
#See anybody could be bad to you you need a good girl to blow your mind #
#bang bang into the room I know you want it#
#Bang bang all over you I'll let you have it#
#wait a minute let me take you there ah-oo#
#Wait a minute till ya,ah#
#bang bang there goes your heart I know you want it#
#Back,back seat of my car I'll let you have it#
#Wait a minute let me take you there#
#wait a minute till ya,ah hey#
#She might have let you hold her hand in school but I'ma show you how to graduate#
#No,I don't need to hear you talk the talk just come and show me what your mama gave#
#Oh yeah you'Ve got a very big shhhh#
#mouth but don't say a thing#
#See anybody could be good to you#
#you need a bad girl to blow your mind#
#Bang bang into the room#
#I know you want it bang bang#
#all over you I'll let you have it#
#Wait a minute let me take you there#
#wait a minute till ya ah hey#
#Bang bang there goes your heart#
#I know you want it#
#back,back seat of my car#
#I'll let you have it#
#Wait a minute let me take you there#
#wait a minute till ya ah hey#
#See anybody could be good to you#
#you need a bad girl to blow your mind,your mind#
#Bang bang into the room#
#I know you want it#
#bang bang all over you#
#I'll let you have it#
#Wait a minute let me take you there#
#wait a minute till ya ah hey#
#Bang bang there goes your heart#
#I know you want it#
#back,back seat of my car#
#I'll let you have it#
#wait a minute let me take you there#
#wait a minute till ya ah hey#
#bang,bang into the room#
#I know you want it#
#bang bang all over you#
#I'll let you have it#
#Wait a minute let me take you there#
#wait a minute till ya ah hey#
请为她们热烈鼓掌
我们为"好声音"的姑娘们感到非常骄傲
Brianna Danica Jane Mia还有Sugar
欢迎你们回来 姑娘们
稍后回来
Mark Ronson与Bruno Mars将会唱翻屋顶
Skinner也来到这里
其中一位决赛选手将会成为冠军
千万别错过
美国好声音
欢迎继续收看 今晚正是紧张关头
我们马上要揭晓谁成为最终冠军
但首先 由曾获得三次格莱美奖的制作人和歌手
与全球最瞩目音乐巨星之一来到舞台上
今晚 他们将要为好声音的舞台
带来他们合作的热播歌曲
准备好享受"Uptown funk"
请欢迎Mark Ronson与Bruno Mars
歌曲: Uptown funk  原唱: Mark Ronson&Bruno Mars
#Bam yeah gotta show the world I have a brand new dance#
#bam yeah#
#gotta show the world I have a brand new danc#
#Bam yeah let me show these girls#
#I have a brand new dance bam yeah#
#Watch me#
#his hit that ice cold#
#Michelle pfeiffer that white gold#
#this one for them hood girls#
#Them good girls straight masterpieces#
#stylin',wilin' livin' it up in the city#
#Got Chucks on with saint Laurent#
#gotta kiss myself I'm so pretty#
#I'm too hot hot damn#
#call the police and the fireman #
#make a dragon wanna retire,man#
#I'm too hot hot damn#
#say my name you know who I am#
#am I bad 'bout that money break it down#
#Girls hit your hallelujah ooh#
#Cause uptown funk gon' give it to ya#
#Saturday night and we in the spot#
#Don't believe me just watch come on#
#Don't believe me just watch#
#Hey,hey,hey,oh stop wait a minute#
#Fill my cup put some liquor in it#
#Take a sip sign the check#
#Julio get the stretch ride to Harlem#
#come on Hollywood#
#come on Jackson Mississippi#
#if we show up#
#we gon' show out smoother than a fresh jar of skippy#
#I'm too hot hot damn#
#call the police and the fireman #
#make a dragon wanna retire,man#
#I'm too hot hot damn#
#say my name you know who I am#
#Girls hit your hallelujah ooh#
#Cause uptown funk gon' give it to ya#
#Saturday night and we in the spot#
#Don't believe me just watch come on#
#Don't believe me just watch#
#break it down#
#America in case you haven't heard#
#uptown funk you up#
#I say come on#
#everybody just dance jump on it#
#if you sexy then flaunt it#
#if you freak out then own it#
#don't go and brag just come show me#
#come on dance jump on it#
#if you sexy then flaunt it#
#don't believe me just watch come on#
#Don't believe me just watc#
#uptown funk you up#
#uptown funk you up say it y'all#
#uptown funk you up get up#
#uptown funk you up#
#uptown funk you up say it y'all#
#uptown funk you up say it y'all##
#uptown funk you up#
#Go#
请为Mark Ronson与Bruno Mars热烈鼓掌
这样进行总决赛才对
谢谢你 Bruno
好了 在一周非常忙碌的彩排中
决赛选手抽时间
为粉丝开了一个小型音乐会
他们沉醉于圣诞节气氛
并收到了一个大惊喜
请看
这一季真的非常赞
我们为四位决赛选手感到骄傲
他们想要为大家送上他们的谢意
我们马上开始吧
由Matt McAndrew为大家献唱"O Christmas tree"
#O Christmas tree O Christmas tree#
#the leaves are so unchanging#
我们都很努力
我们来到这里举行圣诞音乐会
为粉丝献上一点小心意
这就像我提早收到的圣诞礼物
-太好了  -请欢迎Craig Wayne Boyd
#silent night#
#holy night#
我好喜欢你 我一直都很支持Blake战队
这样的精神就对了
Jamison先生
#Joy to the world the saviour reigns#
很高兴能在这里与粉丝们在一起
并为他们签名
圣诞节是个很特别的日子
很高兴能给他们送上点心意
Damien
#Special time of Bethlehem#
今天我满心欢喜
我非常感恩
#We wish you a merry Christmas#
#And a happy new year#
各位 请为我们的四位"好声音"决赛选手鼓掌
我们知道你们这一季有多努力
感谢尼桑汽车的支持 你们都会得到一份特别大礼
一辆全新的汽车
我得到了一部全新的汽车 难以置信
有天籁 发明者 罗格还有全电动的里弗
我要给你们每人派一个这样的红拇指戒指
让大家记得 开车的时候 千万别用手机
进去新车试试吧 还等什么
那些箱子一打开
我就非常期待能进到车里
天啊
我一直和我的姐妹共用一部车
一直想买一部天籁
能让我上学放学更快更方便
我想要家庭车
我一直开一辆破旧的小卡车
能让我的儿子坐后座 保证他的安全
我觉得这是史上最酷的事了
太赞了
-我要选全电动的车  -这百分百全电动的
在我参加节目前
我卖了我的车 就为了录制唱片
现在能拥有自己的车 真的是很酷
我能自己开车参加表演什么的
各位再见了
大家来感谢尼桑汽车的伙伴与朋友吧
他们给予的惊喜 真的太刺激了
现在请各位竖起拇指 红拇指日就是今天
尼桑汽车鼓励大家安全驾驶
现在大家可在推特圈出亲朋好友
鼓励大家一同安全行车
这点非常重要 再次感谢尼桑汽车
今夜的舞台无与伦比
接下来请收看完美合作
南方摇滚歌手将加入自己最爱的乐队
献唱"Sweet Home Alabama"
掌声有请Craig Wayne Boyd以及Lynyrd Skynyrd
来吧 大家一起来
歌曲:Sweet Home Alabama  原唱:Bonfire
#big wheels keep on turning#
#carry me home to see my kin#
#singing songs about the southland#
#I miss alabamy once again#
-#and I think it's a sin yes#
#well I heard mister young sing about her#
#well,I heard ol' Neil put her down#
#well,I hope Neil young will remember#
-是什么呢  -什么呢
#a southern man don't need him around anyhow#
#sweet home Alabama#
#where the skies are so blue#
#Sweet home Alabama#
#lord I'm coming home to you#
#yes,I am#
#in Birmingham they love the governor#
是什么呢
#now we all did what we could do#
#Lord they get me off so much#
是什么呢
#does your conscience bother you,now tell the truth#
#Sweet home Alabama#
#where the skies are so blue#
#lord I'm coming home to you#
#Now muscle shoals has got the swampers#
#And they've been known to pick a song or two#
#Lord they get me off so much#
你觉得呢
#They pick me up when I'm feeling blue,now how about you#
#sweet home Alabama#
#where the skies are so blue,now tell the truth#
#lord,I'm coming home to you#
#I'm coming home#
#Yes,I'm coming home#
来呀
掌声
掌声送给Craig Wayne Boyd以及Lynyrd Skynyrd
谢谢各位
休息后 Meghan Trainor将带来最新热曲"Lips are moving"
另外Jennifer Hudson Jessie J和导师们也将登台表演
当然最后 也将宣布本季冠军
您现在收看的是NBC直播现场 感谢各位观众 不要走开
美国好声音
欢迎回到"好声音"决赛现场
她曾两次获得格莱美奖最佳流行歌手提名
她以一支热曲"All about that bass"捕获了众多粉丝
今晚 她将在"好声音"演唱新单曲"Lips are moving"
热烈欢迎Meghan Trainor
歌曲:Lips are moving 原唱:Meghan Trainor
#if your lips are moving#
#Then you're lyin' lyin',lyin',baby#
来吧 一起来
#If your lips are moving if your lips are moving#
#then you're lyin' lyin',lyin',baby#
#boy,look at me in my face tell me #
#that you're not just about this bass#
#you really think I could be replaced nah,#
I come from outer space#
#and I'm a classy girl#
#I'm a hold it up you're full of something#
#but it ain't love#
#and what we got straight overdue go find somebody new#
#You can buy me diamond earrings#
#and deny-NY-NY NY-NY-NY,deny-NY#
#Yes you can Baby#
#But I smell her on your collar#
#so goodbye-bye-bye bye-bye-bye#
#I know you lie 'cause your lips are moving#
#tell me do you think I'm dumb#
#I might be young but I ain't stupid#
#talking around in circles with your tongue#
#I gave you bass you gave me sweet talk#
#Saying how I'm your number one#
#but I know you lie#
#'cause your lips are moving baby don't you know I'm done#
#Come on say it#
#If your lips are moving if your lips are moving#
#if your lips are moving#
#then you're lyin' lyin',lyin',baby#
#if your lips are moving come on#
#if your lips are moving if your lips are moving#
#Then you're lyin' lyin',lyin',baby#
#Hey,baby don't you bring them tears#
#'cause it's too late too late,baby#
#You only love me when you're here#
#you're so two-faced two-faced,babe#
#You can buy me diamond earrings#
#and deny-NY-NY NY-NY-NY,deny-NY#
#Yes you can Baby#
#But I smell her on your collar#
#so goodbye-bye-bye bye-bye-bye#
#I know you lie 'cause your lips are moving#
#tell me do you think I'm dumb#
#I might be young but I ain't stupid#
#talking around in circles with your tongue I gave you bass#
#You gave me sweet talk saying how I'm your number one#
#but I know you lie 'cause your lips are moving#
#Baby don't you know I'm done come on,say#
#if your lips are moving#
#hey if your lips are moving hey if your lips are moving#
#hey then you're lyin',lyin',lyin'#
-#if your lips are moving all#  -好了
#if your lips are moving#
我想听你们和我一起唱
#If your lips are moving then you're lyin'#
一起来
#I know you lie 'cause your lips are moving#
#tell me do you think I'm dumb#
#I might be young but I ain't stupid#
#talking around in circles with your tongue#
#I gave you bass you gave me sweet talk#
#saying how I'm your number one#
#but I know you lie 'cause your lips are moving#
#Baby don't you know I'm done#
以上为Meghan Trainor精彩演唱
感谢你的到来 Meghan
很有趣的歌曲
下节更精彩 Damien将和音乐大腕Jennifer Hudson
男女组合一同登台
您现在收看的是"好声音"决赛现场 不要走开
美国好声音
欢迎回到现场
距离揭晓冠军还有42分钟
但首先 他是个非常有奉献精神的导师 一位认真的音乐人
但和他一起 就像被丢进了"Adam Levine的音乐魔界" 一起来看
希望自己可以站的更高一点
希望在房梁上荡秋千
我还想站在山顶唱歌
那是因为你现在很确实嗨了 下来 咱们聊聊
Adam心里认为他是个野蛮人
但他内心深处 真的就像是音乐剧场
-525600分钟  -天啊 别唱了
525600分钟 所以 亲爱的啊
Adam真的停不下唱音乐剧
#Here we are. The phantom of the opera.#
听他唱过无数次了
#why are we all singing#
他骨子里是个充满活力的舞者
像这样
他高踢腿
试试
很好 像神奇小马
我觉得Maroon 5要是混不下去了 他可以去百老汇发展
来吧 早上好
知道吗 跳跃是最有效的锻炼方式
-我想看看  -不了 谢谢
我不明白你的意思 你讲故事得让我们明白
如果Adam表演单人音乐剧
音乐剧的名字就应该叫"快看我"
再加上括号 "我的个人秀"
没错
这样
她是一位大牌 全球著名歌星 获过格莱美奖和奥斯卡奖
今晚 她与Adam团队的决赛选手 演唱获格莱美提名的单曲
"It's Your World" 有请Damien和独一无二的Jennifer Hudson
歌曲: It's Your World 原唱: Jennifer Hudson
#anything that you#
#want from me boy you can get it any time#
#any place oh oh I'll be your server#
#your slave your everything you#
#ever wanted baby just make one wish#
#and I'll become your genie your go-getter#
#your bring it back and give it to you babe#
#oh oh I'll walk over#
#that rainbow and deliver to#
#you that pot of gold got the whole earth in a box#
#wrapped with a bow for ya it's your world#
#yeah it's your world baby it's your world baby#
#and everything in it it's your world#
#uh,it's your world baby it's your world#
#Boy if you ask it shall be given#
#It's your world#
再来一遍
#it's your world see a woman#
#like you babe shouldn't have to ask for#
#nothing baby no,no,no#
#You should have the world baby#
#right in the palms of your hands oh,oh#
#Just tell me what to do oh#
#to make your life a better life for you#
#Anything your heart desires baby#
#I believe I can make it happen,baby#
#If it's money you want it's nothing#
#Want me to pay your bills#
#it's nothing buy you nice things#
#it's nothing shopping sprees#
#it's nothing oh,oh,oh,oh#
#it's nothing if you're in need#
#of love it's nothing#
#Boy it don't matter what#
#it's nothing even the moon and#
#stars above it's nothing#
#You can have my house it's nothing#
#you can have my car it's nothing#
#I'll cut it out of me#
#it's nothing and give you#
#my heart it's nothing#
#See the universe it's nothing#
#And all of the planets it's nothing#
#Belong to you it's nothing#
#Just reach up and grab it#
#it's nothing hey#
#it's nothing it's nothing#
#Hey it's your world#
#it's your world baby you deserve#
#the whole world and everything in it#
#It's your world I'm gonna wrap it up#
#and give it to you anything you want#
#anything you need I will surely do#
#It's your world#
-举起手来  -#what you want#
#baby I got it girl believe it#
#It's your world#
#Na na na na na#
#all of your hopes and dreams#
#I'm all about it hey it's your world#
#Yeah and everything#
#and everything in it it's you baby#
#It's your world#
#see you ain't got a question no#
#(All you've got to do...) Because there's no need to ask#
#It's your world it's your world now#
#it's your world baby it's your world yeah#
#it's your world it's your world#
#it's your world#
怎么样
"美国好声音"现场决赛继续 美妙音乐不断
各位 把掌声送给Damien和Jennifer Hudson
她是一位流行歌星 一位母亲 一位时装标志性人物
加入"美国好声音"大家庭的出色成员
她在后台非常勤奋 我们发现Gwen Stefani独一无二
Gwen很棒 她是最平易近人 最踏实的人
谢谢你
亲切 腼腆 人很好
-我好爱你  -我也爱你
她像只小猫
我在想 怎么和Pharrell抢你 我都胃痛了
但她登台后...
#I'm just a girl#
就变成了老虎
她台风霸气
#You looking at me#
像只豹子
猎捕羚羊
移动肩膀 偷偷接近猎物
-非常好  -很好
-像这样...  -对 这样
她富有洞察力 很有型 很懂时尚
-你喜欢时装吗  -喜欢 我爱你的鞋
我喜欢谈论发型 衣服 款式
这部分是牛仔裤 这部分用非洲布料
像缰绳一样包裹
"时尚"有了新的名字 "GWEN"
我想打扮打扮你
她会谈论打扮 说要开睡衣晚会
把T恤给我
如果这些都不管用...
时尚达人
-真希望你能打扮打扮Adam  -见到我的超棒衬衫了吗
Adam有一件不带领子的衬衫
我的发型要是打扮得像Craig 会很怪的
天啊
Gwen 我们爱你
好了 接下来 这位前导师助理获过三次格莱美提名
今晚 他重返"好声音"舞台 为大家带来家喻户晓的歌曲
"Thinking Out Loud" 各位 掌声有请Ed Sheeran
歌曲: Thinking Out Loud 原唱: Ed Sheeran
#When your legs don't work like they used to before#
#and I can't sweep you off of your feet#
#Will your mouth still remember the taste#
#of my love will your eyes still#
#smile from your cheeks darling,I will#
#be lovin' you till we're 70#
#And baby,my heart could still fall as hard#
#at 23 and I'm thinking about how#
#people fall in love in mysterious ways#
#Maybe just the touch of a hand#
#me I fall in love with you every single day#
#And I just wanna tell you I am#
#So honey now take me into#
#your lovin' arms kiss me under the light#
#of a thousand stars place your head#
#on my beating heart I'm thinking out loud#
#maybe we found love right where we are#
#When my hair's all but gone and my memory fades#
#and the crowds don't remember my name#
#When my hands don't play the strings#
#the same way I know you will still#
#love me the same 'cause honey your soul#
#could never grow old it's evergreen#
#And baby,your smile's forever in my#
#mind and memory I'm thinking about how#
#people fall in love in mysterious ways#
#Maybe it's all part of a plan#
#I'll just keep on making the same mistakes#
#Hoping that you'll understand#
#That baby,now take me into your#
#loving arms kiss me under#
#the light of a thousand stars#
#Oh darlin' place your head on#
#my beating heart thinking out loud#
#maybe we found love right where we are#
#Baby we found love right where we are#
#We found love right where we are#
谢谢各位 谢谢
掌声谢谢Ed Sheeran 各位
谢谢Ed 好的 Matt McAndrew在节目里有很多好朋友
当他有机会带回一些人时 他心中已经知道要选谁了
这次的回归演出 我邀请了
Taylor Phelan Mia Pfirrman Taylor John Williams 还有Sugar Joans
来和我演唱Fleetwood Mac的"Go Your Own Way"
我和Taylor之间的情谊 真的很深厚
他的表演 一直都很投入
他的表演 很有魅力 很有共鸣
Mia是Adam队的学员 我跟她关系很好
她唱歌真的很厉害 也会帮助我自己进步
"Royals"是我最喜欢的表演 那首歌简直棒极了
他很了解自己 知道如何在舞台上演唱
也很有自信
让我和其他选手组成组合的话 我应该就会选他
Sugar是我关系很好的一位 她唱歌超有感情的
嗓音也很有穿透力
我一直想和她搭档演唱的 当然要请她回来
这个组里的每一个人我都喜欢
也都很尊敬 他们都是厉害的歌手
我喜欢这样大家族形式的演唱组合
和我的朋友们一起演唱 肯定很好看 我很激动
有请Matt携Sugar Taylor John以及Taylor Phelan带来这首"Go Your Own Way"
歌名: Go Your Own Way 原唱: Fleetwood Mac
#Loving you Isn't the right thing to do#
#How can I ever change things That I feel#
#If I could#
#Maybe I'd give you my world#
#How can I#
#When you won't take it from me#
#You can go your own way#
#Go your own way#
#You can call it Another lonely day#
#Another lonely day#
#You can go your own way#
#Go your own way#
#Tell me why#
#Everything turned around#
#Packing up#
#Shacking up is all you wanna do#
#If I could#
#Baby I'd give you my world#
#Open up#
#Everything's waiting for you#
#You can go your own way#
#Go your own way#
#You can call it#
#Another lonely day#
#You can go your own way#
#Go your own way#
#You can call it#
#Another lonely day#
#Another lonely day
#You can go your own way#
#Go your own way#
#You can call it#
#Another lonely day#
#You can go your own way#
#Go your own way#
谢谢Mia Sugar Taylor John Taylor和Matt
先进一段广告 马上回来
后面精彩继续
这里是NBC好声音冠军揭晓赛现场直播 稍后回来
美国好声音
欢迎回来 这里是好声音最后一场
还有22分钟 冠军就将揭晓 敬请关注
首先呢 Damien将带回几位他一开始就很欣赏的选手
我的回归表演 我邀请了Anita Elyjah还有Danica
来演唱这首"Ain't No Mountain High Enough"
我们都喜欢蓝调音乐 所以...
我们会让大家眼前一亮的
我邀请了Anita 因为她是我最好的朋友之一
我喜欢她的瑞格舞
我好喜欢她唱的那首歌
Elyjah是Pharrell队的 我知道Pharrell也很想念他
他唱歌的时候 总是毫无保留
他才18岁 就已经如此优秀 很难得
等他再长大一点 一定不可估量
Danica情感很充沛 每次登台 都秒杀一片
天哪 这姑娘声音太好听了
我觉得全美观众都要守在电视机前欣赏
这绝对是不可多得的一刻
有请Damien Anita Danica Elyjah
带来这首"Ain't No Mountain High Enough"
歌名: Ain't No Mountain High Enough 原唱: Marvin Gaye
#Listen,baby#
#Ain't no mountain high#
#Ain't no valley low#
#Ain't no river wide enough,baby#
#If you need me,call me#
#No matter where you are#
#No matter how far(don't worry baby)#
#Just call my name#
#I'll be there in a hurry#
#You don't have to worry#
#'Cause baby,#
#There ain't no mountain high enough#
#Ain't no valley low enough#
#Ain't no river wide enough#
#To keep me from getting to you babe#
#Remember the day#
#I set you free#
#I told you#
#You could always count on me darlin'#
#From that day on I made a vow#
#I'll be there when you want me#
#Some way,some how#
#'Cause baby,#
#There ain't no mountain high enough#
#Ain't no valley low enough##
#Ain't no river wide enough#
#To keep me from getting to you babe#
#Oh no darlin'#
#No wind,no rain#
#All winters cold#
#Can't stop me baby (No No Baby)#
#'Cause you are my goal#
#If you're ever in trouble#
#I'll be there on the double#
#Just send for me oh baby#
#My love is alive#
#Way down in my heart#
#Although we are miles apart#
#If you ever need a helping hand#
#I'll be there on the double#
#As fast as I can#
#Don't you know that#
#There ain't no mountain high enough#
#Ain't no valley low enough#
#Ain't no river wide enough#
#To keep me from getting to you babe#
#Don't you know that#
#There ain't no mountain high enough#
#Ain't no valley low enough#
#Ain't no river wide enough#
#To keep me from getting to you babe#
#There ain't no mountain high enough#
#Ain't no valley low enough#
#Ain't no river wide enough#
#To keep me from getting to you babe#
掌声再次送给Anita Danica Elyjah Damien
回来之后 Chris Jamison与Jessie J
导师们将为节日带来一场特别表演
距结果揭晓只有18分钟
稍后敬请关注NBC现场直播
美国好声音
欢迎回到决赛现场
距揭晓"好声音"决赛冠军只有18分钟
在此之前 Chris Jamison将最后一次登台
并联手国际音乐巨星
演唱其最新力作"Masterpiece"
掌声欢迎Chris Jamison和著名的Jessie J
歌名: Masterpiece  原唱: Jessie J
#So much pressure,why so loud?#
#If you don't like my sound you can turn it down#
#I gotta road,and I walk it alone#
Chris 唱
#Uphill battle,I look good when I climb#
#I'm ferocious,precocious I get braggadocios#
#I'm not gonna stop,I like the view from the top#
#you talk that blah blah#
#that la la,that rah rah shit#
#and I'm so done,I'm so over it#
#Sometimes I mess up,I eff up,I hit and miss#
#but I'm okay,I'm cool with it#
#I still fall on my face sometimes#
#and I,can't colour inside the lines#
#cause,I'm perfectly incomplete#
#I'm still working on my masterpiece#
#and I,I wanna hang with the greatest#
#got a way to go,but it's worth the wait#
#no,you haven't seen the best of me#
#I'm still working on my masterpiece#
#oh,oh,oh,ah oh,oh,oh,ah#
#those who mind don't matter#
#those who matter don't mind#
#if you don't catch what I'm throwing#
#then I leave you behind#
#gone in a flash#
#and I am living like that,yeah#
#they talk that blah blah#
#that la la,that rah rah shit#
#go with the punches,and take the hits#
#sometimes I mess up,I eff up,I swing and miss#
#but it's okay,I'm cool with it#
#I still fall on my face sometimes#
#and I can't color inside the lines#
#'cause I'm perfectly incomplete#
#and I'm still working on my masterpiece#
#And I,I wanna hang with the greats#
#got a way to go but it's worth the wait#
#no,you haven't seen the best of me#
#I'm still working on my masterpiece#
#oh,oh,oh,ah oh,oh,oh,ah#
Chris 接着唱
#I still fallon my face sometimes#
#and I can't color inside the lines#
#'cause I'm perfectly incomplete#
#I'm still working on my masterpiece#
#my masterpiece#
#Your masterpiece#
#yeah#
#I still fall I still fall#
#inside the lines#
#I'm perfectly incomplete#
#on my masterpiece#
#oh,oh,oh#
#my masterpiece#
#ah oh,oh,oh,baby#
#working on my masterpiece#
#I'm still working on my masterpiece#
#Yeah#
#ah#
#still working on#
#still working on my masterpiece#
这就是"好声音"决赛
Chris Jamison和优秀的Jessie J
非常感谢你今晚的到来
好了 首先
不容置疑Blake Shelton是个天才
他是个乡村音乐巨星 今年的乡村音乐男音乐家
尽管享有如此光辉
我们却都知道Blake真的在这里
你没法儿按键
没法儿按键
天哪
给点鼓励嘛
我被自己的音乐深深触动了
我不得不说"上帝 谢谢你赐福给我"
赐给我头脑 节奏感
感觉很好
我只是个乡下小子
不知道...
你没法儿按键
我告诉你吧 小子
我们就是这样...
你没法儿按键
看着我的眼睛
-天哪  -你没法儿按键
你们听起来都很过时
你没法儿按键
给我一首歌 一段节奏
我不会出一点错
就是这个意思
超震撼
-很火爆  -选手们卯足了劲儿
向他们学习
90后们要引爆全场了
-要么努力...  -要快
世界等着你们去震撼
停
好戏开始了...
漂亮
马上就要公布冠军了
各位导师将再次联袂登台
献上一曲"Have yourself a merry little Christmas"
有请Pharrell Adam Gwen和Blake
歌曲:Have yourself a merry little Christmas  表演:Pharrell Adam Gwen和Blake
#have yourself a merry little Christmas#
#let your heart be light#
#from now on#
#our troubles will be#
#out of sight#
#have yourself a merry little Christmas#
#make the yuletide gay#
#from now on#
#our troubles will be#
#miles away#
#here we are#
#as in olden days happy golden days of yore#
#faithful friends#
#who are dear to us#
#gather near to us #
#once more#
#through the years#
#we all will be together #
#if the fates allow#
#Hang a shining star upon the highest bough#
#And have yourself a merry little Christmas#
#now#
谢谢各位导师
接下来 将是我们翘首期盼的时刻
别走开
美国好声音
欢迎回来 整整一季的表现中
你们见证了台上四位选手的精彩表现
各位 马上将要揭晓最终的胜利者
Craig Chris Damien Matt
你们中一位的命运将彻底改变
我首先公布的是第四名
请听...
第四名是...
Adam队的Damien
掌声祝贺Damien
现在只剩下Craig Chris和Matt
我即将公布第三名
第三名决赛选手是...
Adam队的Chris Jamison
祝贺你
那现在就只剩下了...
Craig和Matt
你们中一个将夺得好声音冠军
好声音的冠军是...
Craig Wayne Boyd
你是冠军
掌声祝贺Matt McAndrew
掌声祝贺四位选手
请接受奖杯
Craig Wayne Boyd
决赛中的冷门选手
夺得了奖杯
你可以在明早的"今日秀"
和明晚的"今夜秀"中
看到Craig Wayne Boyd
Craig 就要这样
女士们 先生们
他将为我们演唱原创歌曲
即昨晚的"My baby's got a smile on her face"
有请"美国好声音"冠军
Blake队的
Craig Wayne Boyd
歌曲:My baby's got a smile on her face  原唱:Craig Wayne Boyd
#she rolls out of bed#
#and wipes the sleep out of her eyes#
#I know she's bound to be tired#
#but she looks satisfied#
#we stayed up a little late last night#
#I guess I must be doing something right,oh#
#'cause my baby's got a smile on her face#
#my baby's got a smile on her face#
一起来
#as soon as I get to work#
#I call her on the phone#
#oh to tell her that I love her#
#and I can't wait 'til I get home#